ILGWU Legal Department Records 5780/063
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Marlene Industries. Official Report of Proceedings Before the NLRB, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  November 14
- Marlene Industries. Official Report of Proceedings Before the NLRB, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  November 15
- Marlene Industries. Official Report of Proceedings Before the NLRB, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  December 4
- Marlene Industries. Official Report of Proceedings Before the NLRB, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  December 5
- Marlene Industries. Official Report of Proceedings Before the NLRB, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  January 8
- Marlene Industries. Official Report of Proceedings Before the NLRB, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  January 9
- Putterman v. Local 155. Deposition of Violeta Putterman, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  February 21
- Putterman v. Local 155. Deposition of Violeta Putterman, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  February 28
- Putterman v. Local 155. Deposition of Union Sanitorium Association, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  April 18
- Putterman v. Local 155. Deposition of Sol Chaikin, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  September 12
- Putterman v. Local 155. Deposition of Sol Greene, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  November 12
- Putterman v. Local 155. Deposition of Norman Lewis, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Deposition of Willard Aldrich, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Deposition of Salvatore De Angelis, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Transcript of Trial Proceedings, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  June 21
- Putterman v. Local 155. Transcript of Trial Proceedings, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Transcript of Trial Proceedings, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Transcript of Trial Proceedings, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  June 24
- Putterman v. Local 155. Transcript of Trial Proceedings, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  June 27
- Putterman v. Local 155. Transcript of Trial Proceedings, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  June 28
- Putterman v. Local 155. Transcript of Trial Proceedings, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  June 29
- Putterman v. Local 155. Transcript of Trial Proceedings, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  June 30
- Putterman v. Local 155. Transcript of Trial Proceedings, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  July 1
- Putterman v. Local 155. Exhibits, 1969-1983 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  News Clippings Included
- Putterman v. Local 155. Exhibits 1-5, 1970-1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Pamphlets Included
- Putterman v. Local 155. Exhibits 6-20, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Exhibits 20-40, 1970-1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Exhibits 41-68, 1977-1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Grievance Committee, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Motion for Summary Judgement [Folder 1 of 5], 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Motion for Summary Judgement [Folder 2 of 5], 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Motion for Summary Judgement [Folder 3 of 5], 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Motion for Summary Judgement [Folder 4 of 5], 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Motion for Summary Judgement [Folder 5 of 5], 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Court Papers, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Court Papers, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Court Papers, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Court Papers Volume II [Folder 1 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Court Papers Volume II [Folder 2 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Court Papers Volume III [Folder 1 of 3], 1982-1985 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Court Papers Volume III [Folder 2 of 3], 1982-1985 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Court Paper Volume III [Folder 3 of 3], 1982-1985 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Putterman v. Local 155. Judgement, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Rosario v. Amalgamated. Trial Transcript [Folder 1 of 3], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Rosario v. Amalgamated. Trial Transcript [Folder 2 of 3], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Rosario v. Amalgamated. Trial Transcript [Folder 3 of 3], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Rosario v. Amalgamated. Bound Briefs Volume III, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Rosario v. Amalgamated. Bound Briefs Volume II, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Rosario v. Amalgamated. Bound Briefs Volume I, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Rosario v. Amalgamated. Court Papers Volume III, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Rosario v. Amalgamated. Court Papers Volume II, 1978-1981 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Rosario v. Amalgamated. Court Papers Volume I, 1975-1978 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Dee Knitting Mills [Folder 1 of 4], 1974-1980 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Dee Knitting Mills [Folder 2 of 4], 1974-1980 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Dee Knitting Mills [Folder 3 of 4], 1974-1980 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Dee Knitting Mills [Folder 4 of 4], 1974-1980 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Pymm Thermometer Corporation [Folder 1 of 3], 1985 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Pymm Thermometer Corporation [Folder 2 of 3], 1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Pymm Thermometer Corporation [Folder 3 of 3], 1985 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Pymm Thermometer Corporation [Folder 1 of 3], 1986 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Pymm Thermometer Corporation [Folder 2 of 3], 1986 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Pymm Thermometer Corporation [Folder 3 of 3], 1986 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Rose King and Rainbow Knitting, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  Fashion Brand Tags Included
- Rose King and Rainbow Knitting [Folder 1 of 2], 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Rose King and Rainbow Knitting [Folder 2 of 2], 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- San Francisco Joint Board v. NLRB, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 14)